They will do anything to find the truth
The Motel Life is a drama, mystery, thriller film directed by Alan Polsky.
A pair of working-class brothers flee their Reno Motel after
getting involved in a fatal hit-and-run accident.
Frank, played by Emile Hirsch.
Jerry Lee, played by Stephen Dorff.
Annie James, played by Dakota Fanning.
Earl Hurley, played by Kris Kristofferson.
Tommy, played by Joshua Leonard.
Al Casey, played by Noah Harpster.
The Motel Life is a 2012 American drama film starring Emile Hirsch,
Stephen Dorff, Dakota Fanning, and Kris Kristofferson.
Directed and produced by brothers Alan and Gabriel Polsky, the screenplay was adapted by Noah
Harpster and Micah Fitzerman-Blue from Willy Vlautin's novel of the same name.
The film was shot in Gardnerville, Minden, Reno, and Virginia City, Nevada,
and also features animated sequences drawn by Mike Smith.
The film explores themes of sibling relationship,
nevada, motel, hit, on the run.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.